# Resume

# Ajay Arjun Dake

Contact no. 8600860391/8806399709

Email: adake1994@gmail.com / Ajay.dake5@gmail.com

# Career Objective:

The career objective is to learn, Grow and develop in the organization. To demonstrate the values ad skills acquired throughout. To apply the theoretical classroom Knowledge of my Project management at work and achieve the highest level of success and accomplishment. To take initiatives and train allowing exploring & experimenting new things.

# **Professional Summary:**

Self-motivated HR generalist with 3+ years of experience, skilled in employee engagement and training. Seeking to invigorate the corporate culture. Improved managerial performance 23% and implemented a program to gain 100% Employee Engagement and Employee Relations from Past Experience

# **Education**:

Class	Institutions	Marks	Passing year
SSC	Trimurti public school	63%	2010
HSC	Indrayani junior college	44%	2012
B.Sc	Fergusson college	58.00%	2017
MBA (HR)	Prathiba Institute of Business Managemant	50%	2017-2019

#### Skills:

- 1) Good communication, presentation and analytical skills,
- 2) Excellent attention to details,
- 3) Effective listening and fast learning
- 4) Never give up attitude
- 5) Dedication and hardworking
- 6) Self driven, smart work, discipline with level integrity.
- 7) Creative thinking, Time management.
- 8) Working under pressure

# Technical Skills:

Proficient in MS Excel and MS Word

## **Working History:**

#### Working as HR Business Partner at ElasticRun (Jan 2020- Till date):

#### Roles and responsibilities:

- Resolve complex employee relations issues and address grievances.
- Work closely with management and employees to improve work relationships, build morale and increase productivity and retention.
- Provide HR policy guidance.
- Improving and monitoring employee productivity.
- Handling Exit discussion and exit for resigned employees.

## Worked as HR specialist at Fujitsu Consulting India Pvt. Ltd (August 2018- 14 Jan 2020)

#### **Key Accountability:**

- Have in-depth understanding of how own areas integrate within the organization sub-function and basic commercial awareness.
- Process improvement to process Good analytical skills of qualitative information. Coordination and facilitating the work of others

## Job Role and Responsibilities:

- HRSS: Manage Employee relations including handling employee queries.
- Provide current and prospective employee with information and policies, Job duties, work condition and employee relation issues.
- HRIS: Control, maintain and monitor internal HR system and data base.
- Identify ways to improve policies and procedures and assist with the development abd administration of programs.
- <u>Employee Relations</u>: Guide employees and managers through employee relation issues. Guide managers in order to reach appropriate resolutions and demonstrate success in managing complex employees issue.
- Managing and Invoicing processing invoices from HR perspective.

# Worked in BCM Group As HR Recruiter & HR Admin (April 2017 – June 2018). Job Role and Responsibilities:

- Handling end to end recruitment process
- Sourcing, screening, and interview coordination with candidate and client.
- Searching for potential candidates as per the clients & requirement
- Working on different job portals and social media platforms
- Conducting interviews and filtering candidates for open positions
- Filling open positions efficiently and effectively.
- Lining up for short listed candidates and schedules for interviews.
- Continuous follow-ups with the candidates and the clients till the candidates receive the offer letter.
- Conducting interviews of shortlisted candidates for various positions across both ends of spectrum.
- Onboarding of new jonnies.
- Vender management.
- Internal Administration.
- Employees Daily Attendance, Keeping records of employees Leaves & Absences.

# **Certifications:**

- Effectively Managing Employee Performance.
- Team Management
- MAM Orientation
- How o Motivate Employees (So That The Productivity Increases)
- Introduction to Learning and development
- Agile PeopleOps Framework (APF): Foundation
- HR- Analytics- Analytics In Talent Management
- Effective Managing Employees Performance.

# **Achievement:**

- Work on various communities of ventures club for College Fest.
- Completed 2 years NCC Course (Naval wing).
- State and national level karate/ kickboxing champion.

#### Interests:

- Adventure activities such as Treks & Hikes
- Photography
- Traveling

# Personal details:

- Name- Ajay A. Dake
- DOB-09/01/1994
- Address- B-404, Shreeji lake view, Nalbandh Galli, Tal. Maval. Dist. Pune.
- Language known: English, Hindi, Marathi